mycfe.com 2016-04-07

# FACTS

      About            Printing Requirements           Reset         Show Field Borders
                                                                                                                                    Rev. 08/2013
                               WHAT DOES CFE FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
 FACTS                         INFORMATION?
 Why?                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                               the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                               share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we
                               do.
 What?                         The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                               with us. This information can include:
                                 l Social Security number                                    l Transaction history
                                 l Account balances                                          l Account transactions
                                 l Payment history                                           l Checking account information
                               When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
 How?                          All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business.
                               In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal
                               information; the reasons CFE Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this
                               sharing.
    Reasons we can share your personal information                              Does CFE FCU share?              Can you limit this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes -                                                          Yes                          No
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your
 account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes -                                                                  Yes                          No
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                            Yes                          No
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                               No                     We don't share
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                               No                     We don't share
 information about your creditworthiness
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                             No                     We don't share
 Questions?                    Call 407- 896-9411 or outside Orlando 800-771-9411 option 3 or go to MyCFE.com
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                        PRIV-MODEL 8/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                               2012.1/0648 3800520-010 Custom EPRV0648

Page 2
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?          CFE Federal Credit Union means Central Florida Educators' Federal Credit Union.
What We Do
How does CFE FCU protect my            To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
personal information?                  security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
                                       safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                       We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect
                                       this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom
                                       access is appropriate.
How does CFE FCU collect my            We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?                    l Open an account                          l Apply for financing
                                         l Apply for a loan                         l Show your driver's license
                                         l Provide employment information
                                       We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                       affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?         Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                         l sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your
                                            creditworthiness
                                         l affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                         l sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                       State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                       See below for more on your rights under state law.
Definitions
Affiliates                             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                       nonfinancial companies.
                                         l CFE Federal Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.
Nonaffiliates                          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                       nonfinancial companies.
                                         l CFE Federal Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market
                                            to you.
Joint Marketing                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                       financial products or services to you.
                                         l Our joint marketing partners include insurance and credit card companies.
Other Important Information
We will not disclose information about you to anyone or information about former members, except as permitted by law.
For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Members. We will not share personal information with
nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
For California Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or
for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with
our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Members. We will not share personal information from deposit or
share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
For Vermont Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates for them to market to you without
your authorization and we will not share personal information with affiliates or for joint marketing about your
creditworthiness without your authorization.
